But far too far apart, Mr. Chris General.
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for you and we're thankful for this community that we get to live in and we're thankful for.
Council members who are willing to serve to make hard decisions for the community.
We'll just ask that you give them wisdom and guidance as they do business tonight.
It's in your name we pray.
Amen.
I'd like to introduce you to the flag of the United States of America.
To the Republic for which this stands.
One nation, another guy in the visible liberty and justice for all.
Four public input unskilled personal practices, five claims list.
Most two approved.
Second.
Was he supposed to abstain from that?
No.
Second.
Oh.
8, budget amendment 24, 19, transferring MSUA, budgeted grant and donations along with the
actual fund transfers for previous fiscal years for the general fund, from the general
fund grants, donations fund to the MSUA grants donations fund.
Okay, clear as a matter of time.
So this stems from a conversation with the city attorney that we want to make sure we
keep approval of expenditures and revenues very separate from the trust in the council,
two totally different companies, totally just different.
This move, so originally we just had a grants and donations fund that everybody was
in, including MSUA.
This moves MSUA's grants and donations to its own fund, which was created this year when
we brought over the money for the donations for the Christmas decoration.
So those are already in that fund that this moves all of the grant and donation activity
to this fund.
So where's the Christmas fund?
It is in this fund, fund 512.
So you're putting everything in the same fund.
There's a lot of different account numbers. There's a lot of different revenues and expenditures
But this is just the grants and donations not it does not include the Christmas decorations because they're already in
Yes, and you'll see this on the council side too
Second
Hi
This will be here 24.5 budget by state statute. Oh
trust
called authorities they have to
provide
A budget to the governing to the beneficiary, which is the city and this
What's in your packet is a budget summary just for MSU A none of the numbers have changed since the presentation on May 21st at the Colour and these are the four funds that are
MSU A it's
Literally the MSU A special utility authority fund 510 and then 511 which is stormwater
That's where our stormwater fee goes in. There's one person in that fund that works out of that fund
The improve it fund. That's where some of our loans and bonds have gone and then there's the 512 MSU A grants and donations fund
The total for all four of those is 48 million
1393 dollars make motion we approve
10 contract
Amendment number one for annual six months as needed
I agree it rock supply
C 23 dash fit nine with Kimstone. It did a positive mission of all required contract documents trust ease and chairman
We only had Kimstone come in on this on this one design the end of the amendment and we recommend that the
City of Lima except the amendment and the MSU A
for Kim Stone.
Joe and I.
Goodman.
Hi.
He's Seth Parker.
Good question on that, Brian.
And it's not a change in my boat or anything.
But do we ever have anybody else bid on that?
Well, this one, we just needed to get the amendment signed.
But we sent out solicitations.
And this is the one that came back.
We're seeing more and more of that.
We're still trying to work on a concrete company right now
for another area that had always bid.
And sometimes they just act like they don't have enough time and various things.
It's interesting.
Yeah, sure.
OK.
I love a contract.
Amendment number one for annual six months as needs concrete, sand, supply,
sea 23-60 with Muscogee sand,
continue the policy mission of all required contract documents.
And this one, again, staff recommends that the city of Miami and the MSU
accept amendment one or C23-60 from and for Muscogee sand.
Are there the only one as well?
Yep.
So a recent significant price increases in these only bid only.
Now it's about the same.
Generally, we have had a few increases.
No, we're not seeing anything that's really a trend.
No, like, yeah.
OK.
Most of you approve?
He's said, all right.
So folks.
All right.
James.
Hi.
Well, we're an annual as needed on call, open trench and boring labor for water line or replacement
C24-18 for fiscal year 2425 to M&J equipment services,
common construction, B-town construction, LLC, and broadband head,
boring LLC is recommended by staff, proof contract, continuing on suspicion of all required
contract documents and authorized the interim
trust manager or as does it need a side note as you can see.
On this particular one, we did have a number of people that were involved and submitted.
On this particular one, what we do is if a project's needed, we will go with the lowest one first.
And if their booked up and can't get to it, we go to the next one and so on.
But it's nice to have a group like this that we don't have to stop everything and have, quote,
each time and all.
So it's the staff recommendation to accept the all-bits turned in and use them on an as needed
basis to best benefit the city MSUI.
motion to approve.
Sake.
Dopple.
The next.
Jones.
Pick them.
Hi.
Parker.
13 award.
High voltage, line clearance, tree trimming and tree revocers.
This C24-29 for fiscal year 2425, to pro tree management.
As recommended by staff, approve the contractative in a pond.
Submission of all of our contract documents and on the rise is in terms of trust
or his doesn't need to receive.
We did have multiple beds on this particular one.
Pro tree management came in and won it.
It's a staff's recommendation to approve 24-19
for pro tree management to best benefit the city.
Most to approve.
I'll sign up.
He's the doctor.
Go for him.
Joe, I'm a victim.
Hi.
Park, Park.
Thank you.
Thank you, Brock.
Fourteen out of the new business of any which
of the businesses, posting of this agenda.
15 staff reports, 16 trustee community announcements,
17.
This meeting will be continued from council chambers
to reconvene the staff room for the purpose
of executive session.
The question of agenda item number six of the regular meeting
of the amount of city card of the MIPFA.